# Valentine Orga

https://valentineorga.vercel.app / https://github.com/ValentineCodes / https://x.com/ValentineOrga / www.linkedin.com/in/valentineorga

Awka, Anambra Nigeria +2348140715721 Valentineorga@gmail.com

#### **ABOUT ME**

What started out as a passion over 4 years ago has succeeded in being my career. I've worked on multiple projects with startups and companies in the web2 space as a mobile and web developer. Now I'm fully dedicated to creating a meaningful impact in the web3 space.

## **EXPERIENCE**

# **Clynto**, USA — Blockchain Developer

**JULY 2024 - SEPTEMBER 2024** 

## https://clynto.com

Built the smart contracts for a P2P lending and borrowing protocol, enabling loan creation, funding, repayment, and liquidation across multiple tokens. Additionally, implemented a governance system utilizing CLY tokens for voting.

# **BuidlGuidl**, USA — Blockchain Developer

MARCH 2023 - JANUARY 2024

Scaffold-ETH-Mobile

# https://github.com/ValentineCodes/scaffold-eth-mobile

Built an open-source toolkit for building mobile decentralized applications seamlessly using React Native & Foundry/Hardhat; Built with React Native, Foundry, Hardhat, Ganache, Ethersjs, e.t.c

**Yield: A Liquid Restaking Protocol** 

## https://github.com/ValentineCodes/vield

Built a protocol which enables users to stake stETH into Eigenlayer to earn extra rewards. Admins(a multisig wallet) can delegate and undelegate to an operator and also withdraw assets. Built with Next.js, Solidity, Ethersjs, WalletConnect, e.t.c

## Paux Wallet

# https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.paux.wallet

Built a safe and secure crypto wallet to generate accounts, manage tokens, transfer funds, interact with dApps and more on multiple EVM-compatible chains. Built with React Native, WalletConnect, e.t.c

## **SKILLS**

Solidity

**Typescript** 

React Native

Next.js

TailwindCss

Redux

Firebase

Git | Github

#### **ACHIEVEMENTS**

Top 10 in Gitcoin x Lukso
Grants Program with Kitso a variation of
Scaffold-ETH-Mobile for
Lukso

**GG22 OSS Program Grantee** with **Scaffold-ETH-Mobile** 

BuidlGuidl Extensions Hackathon Winner with Universal Profile Extension

## **EDUCATION**

Nnamdi Azikiwe University, Nigeria — Computer Science

OCTOBER 2017 - DECEMBER 2023

# DevRel University by Bianca Buzea

OCTOBER 2024 - DECEMBER 2024